Guide to the Stanford University, Computer Science Department, HCI Group, CS547 Seminar Videorecordings
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Videorecordings
  - Technology and Human Well-Being, Neil Scott, Archimedes Project, Stanford, 2002-5-10; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Neil Scott, Archimedes Project, Stanford, "Technology and Human Well-being" (CS547 Winograd 6), 2002-5-10; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 7)
  - Design of a Video Auditorium and Leveraging the Asymmetric Sensitivity of Eye Contact for Videoconferencing, Milton Chen, Stanford CS, 2002-5-17; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Milton Chen, Stanford Computer Science, "Design of a Video Auditorium and Leveraging the Asymmetric Sensitivity of Eye Contact for Videoconferencing" (CS547 Winograd 7), 2002-5-17; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 7)
  - Designing for the Disadvantaged, Jim Fruchterman, Benetech, 2002-5-24; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Jim Fruchterman, Benetech, "Designing for the Disadvantaged" (CS547 Winograd 8), 2002-5-24; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 7)
  - Intelligence Augmentation: Creating a Prosthetic for the Brain, Bradley Rhodes, Ricoh Innovations, 2002-5-3; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Bradley Rhodes, Ricoh Innivations, "Intelligence Augmentation: Creating a Prosthetic for the Brain" (CS547 Winograd 5), 2002-5-3; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 7)
  - Where Do Web Sites Come From?, Scott Klemmer, Berkeley CS, 2002-5-31; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Scott Klemmer, Berkeley Computer Science, "Where Do Web Sites Come From?" (CS547 Winograd 9), 2002-5-31; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 7)
  - Video Interfaces for Entertainment, Richard Marks, Sony, 2002-9-27; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Richard Marks, Sony, "Video Interfaces for Entertainment" (CS547 Winograd 1), 2002-9-27; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 7)
  - Raj Reddy, Carnegie Mellon University, "The Million Book Digital Library Project" (CS547 Winograd 3), 2003-10-10; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
  - Polle Zellweger, MacZell Consulting, "Making the World Wide Web Fit People: Traveling in Comfort on the Information Superhighway" (CS547 Winograd 4), 2003-10-17; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
  - Bill Moggridge, Designing Technology - was at IDEO (CS547 Winograd 2), 2003-10-3; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 9)
  - Ramesh Raskar, Mitsubishi (MERL), "Graphics, Vision and HCI Research at MERL" (CS547 Winograd 6), 2003-10-31; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
  - Sociable Media for Real and Virtual Spaces, Judith Donath, MIT Media Lab, 2003-1-10; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Judith Donath, MIT Media Lab, "Sociable media for real and virtual spaces" (CS547 Winograd 1), 2003-1-10; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 9)
  - Michael Slater, Adobe, "A Next-Generation Consumer Photo Application: Challenges in Creating Simple Yet Powerful" (CS547 Winograd 8), 2003-11-14; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
  - Jim Hollan, UCSD Cognitive Science, "People, Computers, and Design: A View from UCSD" (CS547 Winograd 9), 2003-11-21; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
  - Tom Zimmerman, IBM Almaden Research, "Motivation for Invention" (CS547 Winograd 7), 2003-11-7; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
  - The How and Why of Google UI, Marissa Mayer, Google, 2003-1-17; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Marissa Mayer, Google, "The How And Why of Google UI" (CS547 Winograd 2), 2003-1-17; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 9)
  - Issues in Personalizing Shared Ubiquitous Interfaces, David Hilbert, FX Palo Alto Laboratory, 2003-1-24; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Issues in Personalizing Shared Ubiquitous Interfaces, Jonathan Trevor, FX Palo Alto Laboratory, 2003-1-24; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - David Hilbert, Jonathan Trevor, FX Palo Alto Laboratory, "Issues in Personalizing Shared Ubiquitous Interfaces" (CS547 Winograd 3), 2003-1-24; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 9)
  - Francois Guimbretiere, University of Maryland, "People Paper and Computers" (CS547 Winograd 10), 2003-12-5; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
  - Using Words to Search a Thousand Images: Hierarchical Faceted Metadata in Search Interfaces, Marti Hearst, UC Berkeley SIMS, 2003-1-31; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Marti Hearst, UC Berkeley SIMS, "Using Words to Search a Thousand Images: Hierarchical Faceted Metadata in Search Interfaces" (CS547 Winograd 4), 2003-1-31; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 9)
  - TaskMaster: Resource management in an email client, Ian Smith, PARC, 2003-2-14; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - TaskMaster: Resource management in an email client, Mark Howard, PARC, 2003-2-14; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - TaskMaster: REsource management in an email client, Nicolas Ducheneaut, PARC, 2003-2-14; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - TaskMaster: Resource management in an email client, Victoria Bellotti, PARC, 2003-2-14; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Ian Smith, Mark Howard, Nicolas Ducheneaut, Victoria Bellotti, PARC, "TaskMaster: Resource management in an email client" (CS547 Winograd 6), 2003-2-14; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 9)
  - Using Computers to Change What People Think and Do: Insights into Captology, BJ Fogg, Stanford CSLI, 2003-2-21; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - BJ Fogg, Stanford CSLI, "Using Computers to Change What People Think and Do: Insights into Captology" (CS547 Winograd 7), 2003-2-21; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 9)
  - Searching Spoken Word Collections, Doug Oard, University of Maryland, 2003-2-28; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Doug Oard, University of Maryland, "Searching Spoken Word Collections" (CS547 Winograd 8), 2003-2-28; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 9)
  - Where do HCI Theory and Practice Meet?, Terry Winograd, Stanford Computer Science, 2003-2-7; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Terry Winograd, Stanford Computer Science, "Where Do HCI Theory and Practice Meet?" (CS547 Winograd 5), 2003-2-7; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 9)
  - Technology Demonstrations: What are they for?, Wally Smith, Edith Cowan University, Western Australia, 2003-3-14; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Wally Smith, Edith Cowan University, Western Australia, "Technology Demonstrations: What are they for?" (CS547 Winograd 10), 2003-3-14; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 9)
  - Art Therapy and Tele-Mediated Communication in Behavioral Telehealth, Kate Collie, University of British Columbia, 2003-3-7; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Kate Collie, University of British Columbia, "Art Therapy and Tele-Mediated Communication in Behavioral Telehealth" (CS547 Winograd 9), 2003-3-7; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 9)
  - Fred Turner, Standford Dept. of Communications, "From Counterculture To Cyberculture: How The Whole Earth Catalog Brought Us "Virtual Community" "(CS547 Winograd 2), 2003-4-11; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 9)
  - Bay-Wei Chang, Google, "Web Search Engines: Algorithms and User Interfaces" (CS547 Winograd 3), 2003-4-18; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 9)
  - Alan Kay, HP Labs, "Croquet: A Collaboration Architecture" (CS547 Winograd 4), 2003-4-25; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 9)
  - There Avatar-centric Communication in There, Chuck Clanton, Jeffrey Ventrella, 2003-4-4; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Chuck Clanton, "There Avatar-centric Communication in There" (CS547 Winograd 1), 2003-4-4; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 9)
  - Ka-Ping Yee, UC Berkeley Computer Science, "Peephole Displays: Pen Interaction on Spatially Aware Handheld Computers" (CS547 Winograd 7), 2003-5-16; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 9)
  - Will Wright, Maxis, "Games and Simulation" (CS547 Winograd 5), 2003-5-2; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 9)
  - Michael Mills, Roy Pea, Stanford Center for Innovations in Learning, "DIVER: (Digital Interactive Video Exploration and Reflection)" (CS547 Winograd 8), 2003-5-23; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 9)
  - Rob Barrett, IBM Almaden Research, "System Administrators are Users Too" (CS547 Winograd 9), 2003-5-30; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 9)
  - Brian Dear, "Lessons Learned: Interacting with the PLATO System" (CS547 Winograd 6), 2003-5-9; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 9)
  - Jeremy Bailenson, Stanford Communication Dept., "Strategic Behavioral Transformations in Immersive Collaborative Virtual Environments" (CS547 Winograd 1), 2003-9-26; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 9)
  - Amy Jo Kim, Principal, SocialDesign.Net, "The Network is the Game: Social Trends in Mobile Entertainment" (CS547 Winograd 1), 2004-10-1; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
  - Scott Snibbe, "Body, Space and Cinema" (CS547 Winograd 3), 2004-10-15; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 9)
  - Ken Hinckley, Microsoft Research, "High Performance Pen Interfaces" (CS547 Winograd 4), 2004-10-22; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 9)
  - Jason Tester, "Accelerated Democracy: Scenarios for the future of technological voting" (CS547 Winograd 5), 2004-10-29; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 9)
  - Scott Kim, "Paper, Plastic, or Playstation? Adapting a game to wide range of technologies" (CS547 Winograd 2), 2004-10-8; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
  - Michael Shiloh, Makingthings.com, "Teleo: Rapid Prototyping Toolkit" (CS547 Winograd 7), 2004-11-12; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
  - James Landay, University of Washington and Intel, "Digital Simplicity: Usable Personal Ubicomp" (CS547 Winograd 8), 2004-11-19; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
  - Mark Newman, PARC, "End-User Composition in Ubiquitous Computing Environments" (CS547 Winograd 6), 2004-11-5; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 9)
  - David Stork, Ricoh and Open Mind Initiative, "The Open Mind Initiative: Large-scale known acquisition from non-experts via the web" (CS547 Winograd 2), 2004-1-16; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
  - Eric Paulos, INTEL Berkeley Lab, "Trash Talk: Deconstructing Situations across our Emerging Technological Urban Landscape" (CS547 Winograd 9), 2004-12-3; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
  - Dan Gillette, Cure Autism Now, "Developing a Voice Output Communication Aid for Children with Severe Autism" (CS547 Winograd 3), 2004-1-23; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
  - Genevieve Bell, Intel Research, "Talking phones: a cultural analysis of an information and communication technology" (CS547 Winograd 4), 2004-1-30; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
  - Jeff Johnson, UI Wizards, "Web Bloopers: Avoiding Common Design Mistakes" (CS547 Winograd 1), 2004-1-9; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
  - Jeffrey Herman, Suja Raju, eBay, "The Business of User Experience" (CS547 Winograd 6), 2004-2-20; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
  - Joan Walton, Leslie Keely, Ronald Mak, NASA Ames Research Center, "NASA's Collaborative Information Portal: HCI Lessons Learned" (CS547 Winograd 7), 2004-2-27; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
  - wk#1832 (CS547 Winograd 9), 2004-3-12; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
  - Jason Hong, UC Berkeley, "Privacy in the Age of Ubiquitous Computing" (CS547 Winograd 8), 2004-3-5; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
  - Simon Buckingham Shum, Knowledge Media Institute, The Open University, UK, "Semantic Scholarly Publishing and Discourse: Tools for Modeling Contested Knowledge Domains" (CS547 Winograd 3), 2004-4-16; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
  - Marc Davis, UC Berkeley, "Mobile Media Metadata: The Future of Mobile Imaging" (CS547 Winograd 1), 2004-4-2; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
  - Mor Naaman, Stanford CS, "Adventures in Time and Space: Leveraging Geo-Referenced Digital Photographs" (CS547 Winograd 4), 2004-4-23; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
  - Jay Trimble, NASA Ames, "MERBoard: a Multi-mission Platform for Collaborative Mission Control Application" (CS547 Winograd 2), 2004-4-9; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 9)
  - Alonso Vera, Roxana Wales, NASA Ames, "Collaboration, Tool Use and Work Practice of Mars Mission Scientists" (CS547 Winograd 6), 2004-5-14; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
  - Anind Dey, Intel Research and UC Berkeley, "Giving Users Control in Ubiquitous Computing Environments" (CS547 Winograd 7), 2004-5-21; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
  - Jennifer Mankoff, UC Berkeley, "Enhancing User Experiences in Ubiquitous Computing" (CS547 Winograd 8), 2004-5-28; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
  - Walt Scacchi, UC Irvine, "Understanding the Requirements for Developing and Designing Free/Open Source Software" (CS547 Winograd 5), 2004-5-7; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
  - Tessa Lau, IBM Research, "Adaptive user interfaces: design challenges for HCI" (CS547 Winograd 2), 2005-1-14; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
  - Ian Smith, Intel Research Seattle, "Social Mobile Applications, Location Privacy and the Capital of Nevada" (CS547 Winograd 3), 2005-1-21; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
  - Margaret Morris, Intel, "Embedded Health Assessment" (CS547 Winograd 4), 2005-1-28; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
  - Merrie Morris, Stanford Computer Science, "Tabletop interfaces" (CS547 Winograd 1), 2005-1-7; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
  - Aaron Marcus, Aaron Marcus and Associates, "12 myths of Mobile Device UI's" (CS547 Winograd 6), 2005-2-11; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
  - Asaf Degani, NASA Ames, "Taming HAL" (CS547 Winograd 7), 2005-2-18; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
  - Ken Goldberg, UC Berkeley, "Networked Robots" (CS547 Winograd 8), 2005-2-25; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
  - Danah Boyd, UC Berkeley SIMS, "Revenge of the Social Network: Lessons from Friendster" (CS547 Winograd 5), 2005-2-4; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
  - Erika Chuang, VSee Lab, "How to Chang the World and be Home for Dinner: The art, science, and myths of videoconferencing" (CS547 Winograd 10), 2005-3-11; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
  - John Woodfill, Tyzx, "Network of Smart 3D sensors" (CS547 Winograd 9), 2005-3-4; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
  - Thad Starner, Georgia Tech, "Wearable computers" (CS547 Winograd 1), 2005-4-1; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
  - Brinda Dalal, Danny Bobrow, Jim Thornton, Nathan Good, Victoria Bellotti, PARC, "What a To-Do: Studies of Task Management Towards the Design of a Personal Task List Manager" (CS547 Winograd 3), 2005-4-15; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
  - Tom Moran, IBM Almaden, "Unified Activity as a Paradigm for Supporting Collaboration" (CS547 Winograd 5), 2005-4-22; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
  - Bill Tomlinson, UC Irvine, "Affective Interaction Paradigms for Animated Characters" (CS547 Winograd 6), 2005-4-29; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
  - Per Persson, Younghee Jung, Nokia, "Mobile Social Computing - From Research to Products" (CS547 Winograd 2), 2005-4-8; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
  - Elaine Chew, USC, "Collaborative Performance Experiments in the Distributed Immersive Performance Project" (CS547 Winograd 8), 2005-5-13; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
  - Ted Selker, MIT Media Lab, "Context-Aware Computing: A World That Knows What To Do For You" (CS547 Winograd 9), 2005-5-20; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
  - Paul Braund, World Bank Institute, "Pilot projects from around the world. The edge of the network society" (CS547 Winograd 10), 2005-5-27; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
  - Ahmad Mansur, Zeum, "Interaction and Exhibit Design in Museums" (CS547 Winograd 7), 2005-5-6; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)